quvarsity.com 2010-06-15

# ProRetention-Student retention software

## Highlights

  1. Gives You Foresight About Student Intentions
  2. Helps Resolve Student Issues
  3. A Repository of All Academic and Administrative Information
  4. Incredible and meaningful real-time dashboard

## Your Privacy is important to us!

This statement discloses information practices for www.proretention.com, including the type of information gathered and tracked, how information is used, and with whom the information is shared.

## Personal Information

You can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. While our site does collect information such as IP address, browser type and operating system, this information does not personally identify you. We collect this information to help us understand our overall audience and improve our site performance.

To download our products or request information, you may be requested to provide personal information, such as your name, telephone number, address and e-mail address.

## Security and Quality of Information

ProRetention™ values the privacy and integrity of your personal information. In order to safeguard this information, we have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as using encryption for transmission of information to help us keep ensure all information we collect remains secure, accurate, current, and complete.

## Marketing Use

ProRetention™ may use the information you provide on our website for marketing purposes, such as understanding your product requirement or whether your search for information was satisfactory. We may get in touch with you either by calling you on the telephone number provided by you and/or through email. If you have agreed to receive updates from ProRetention™, you will receive regular emails regarding new product lines, release updates, or company news. You can at any point opt-out of receiving email updates from ProRetention™.

## Notification of Changes

This privacy statement was last updated on 01-Dec-2009

## Questions regarding this Statement

If you have any questions about our policy, or you believe ProRetention™. has violated the policy, please send an email to [info@proretention.com](mailto:info@proretention.com)

## STUDENT PORTAL

Strong student relationships form the crux of successful retention programs. **[ProRetention™](http://www.proretention.com/proretention_architecture.html "College Students Retention Software")** Student Portal (SEP) is the virtual space where all student activities are available for future reference. And this is where students and university staff meet and get to know each other better.

  * Student-Profile Update
  * Student-Contact preference
  * Lifecycle Information
  * Problem Ticket
  * Announcements
  * Events and Calendar
  * Articles
  * Forum
  * Future Plans

Read More 

Downloads

  * Download Brochure
  * Featured Case Study1
  * Featured Case Study2

Follow us on:
